[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：接下来的两个练习，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The next two exercises,
我实际上要一起布置练习五和练习六。
I'm actually gonna assign exercise five and six together.
他们是这样的，练习五和练习三完全一样。
And here's what they are, exercise five is exactly the same thing as exercise three.
还记得我们做过承诺链吗？
Remember we did the promise chain?
但是现在练习五邀请你使用一个序列来创建一个链。
But now exercise five invites you to use a sequence to create a chain.
练习六和练习四完全一样，
Exercise six is exactly the same as exercise four,
我们做了地图绘制和减少。
where we did map and reduce.
但它邀请您以循环方式使用序列，并且
But it invites you to use a sequence in a looping fashion, and
你会发现这更容易做到。
you'll find out that it's easier to do.
你甚至不需要减少，你可以用一个序列用两个贴图来做。
You don't even need to reduce, you can do it with two maps using a sequence.
所以这两个练习都是为了给你一些时间让你变得更舒服
So both of those exercises are designed to give you some time to get more comfortable
与使用它的序列一起使用，以便我们可以在其余部分中使用它。
with a sequence using it, so that we can use it throughout the rest.
我要说的是，基本上我们要做的就是停下来
I will say this, basically what we're gonna do is just stop for
接下来的20分钟让你练习。
the next 20 minutes to let you work on the exercises.
如果您已经熟悉一个序列，或者
If you're already familiar with a sequence, or
如果你真的不关心它，那就把这两个练习看作是可选的。
if you don't really care about it, consider the two exercises optional.
但它们的设计目的是让你回去做你刚刚做的事情，但是
But they are designed to let you go back and do what you just did but
用一个序列来使它变得更加熟悉。
with a sequence to kind to get more familiar with it.
因此，您应该能够比较三个和五个解决方案，并且
So you should be able to compare the solutions between three and five, and
四个和六个，非常直截了当。
four and six, pretty straightforwardly.